Hey everyone, thanks for listening to
the Grow Your Life podcast. My name is
Jeremiah Herowski and on this podcast I
help coaches, mentors, and trainers to
scale their businesses to make far more
money than they ever thought was
possible in record time. I've been
building online coaching and course
businesses with some of the best
coaches, mentors, and trainers online
for the last 22 years. And I know
exactly what it takes to go from where
you are to where to make the kind of
money that you want to make. Now, every
single week inside of my Wealthy Coach
Academy program, I'm mentoring coaches
and trainers like yourself, and I'd love
to see you become a part of that. You
can find a link below on how to find out
information on that. Today, let's talk
about your niche. Let's talk about
getting that dialed in. It's one of the
number one needle movers that you can
have inside of your business. One of the
biggest things that determines if you're
going to make the kind of money that you
want to make, and I'm not necessarily
talking about just like, let's find your
niche, find your niche. It's finding the
exact people who are going to be buyers
for you. That's what we want to do. We
want to figure out who are those buyers
because you can look at all of the
people that are out there that are
potential in your business, but there's
only a small segment right here that are
really, really just juicy and great for
you that you want to work with that are
going to generate you a lot of money in
your business. And so what I'll do is I
will say I while these are all great
people out here, I'm going to not care
about all of those people, I want to
focus in on who are the best people that
I'm meant to work with. And so couple of
practices that I'll do is I will
visualize and imagine myself working
with my best client. Who are those
people that I want to work with that I
know are going to produce the best
results? Now, if you don't know who your
best client is, you want to listen to
the people that you're already working
with right now. Now, two things. Group
coaching businesses are some of the best
ways to make the kind of money that you
want to make and have the time freedom
that you want to have. And so, you want
to develop a group coaching program
where you're not working one on-one with
just one specific type of person, but
you're able to work with a group of
people to help them on that level. And
so when you figure out who fits into
this specific category of people, that's
going to help you the most. Now, if
you're trying to figure out, okay, who's
the best niche for me? I use artificial
intelligence to be able to do this.
There's a couple of different chat GBT
um prompts that we can do to play around
with to get some great ideas for our
niche. I'm going to show you how to do
that right right now. I'm going to show
you exactly the chat GBT prompts that we
use, exactly what we type in to get some
great ideas for your niche in your
business. So again, if we go over to
chat GBT, we're going to type in, I want
to build a coaching or course business
online to promote with social media.
Generate me 100 niches I could promote
in. And listen, my spelling wasn't
perfect there, but it it definitely does
generate uh a good result right here.
Here's 100 profitable niches. You could
do different business and marketing
niches right here. Here's money and
career, health and wellness, mindset and
personal growth, relationship and
family, spirituality and purpose,
creative and artistic, tech and digital
skills,
lifestyle and hobbies, social impact and
community. And again, these are all just
some niches that you could do. A lot of
these are very subcategory niches like
evergreen email nurture sequences that
might go under marketing that might go
under sending out email marketing, high
ticket webinar funnels. And these are
all great and this a lot of this is
actually based off of some of the things
that it knows about me because I've been
talking with chat GBT about those
things. But what you want to do is you
want to figure out what is the subniche
of a subniche that I want to work in.
And that's really what you're going to
look at. You're going to look at what is
that subniche. For me specifically,
I work almost exclusively with coaches,
mentors, trainers, people that are
really, really good at mentoring people
and they've been doing it a long time.
These are my best clients, but they're
struggling to get more clients online.
They're struggling to get more leads,
more people that are wanting to buy
their services, and they want to package
it in a way that's a group coaching
program that they can not have to work
hundreds of hours themselves, but that
they can help multiple people in a group
program to be able to do that. And then
how do they scale that to make multiple
six and even seven figures? And so
that's the niche in my business that I
work with every single week is I work
with that group of people specifically.
I could talk about, okay, all the people
that are out there that are on the
internet completely. Everybody who's
online, there's a lot of people that are
trying to make money online, right? From
crypto traders to drop shippers, but I'm
not looking to help just everybody who's
on the internet. And I'm not looking to
just help everybody who's trying to sell
stuff online either, from e-commerce to
healthcare and things like that. I want
to specifically focus in on who are the
people that are mentors and coaches
that are helping others mentor and coach
other people on how to do that and how
to use the tools of marketing and
specifically how to use Facebook ads,
how to use social media and how to get
the right people in front of them at the
right time to buy their stuff. And so
that's the subniche that I've developed.
I figured out who is the specific
person. That's is one of the things you
want to write down. Niche is not what,
it's who.
Sure, when we talk about our niche,
there's a lot of what involved, but who
is the person
who's going to be doing that thing
inside of that niche. And that's where
you're going to find the profitability.
That's the needle mover for you is
figuring out who those people are. The
more people that you connect with, the
more people that you talk to on a
regular basis, you're going to be able
to figure out who are my people? Who are
my people that I want to work with
consistently in my business? And so then
what you do is you develop based on
their
desires.
And this one's a big one because oftent
times most coaches and mentors, they're
giving information to people based on
what they believe is going to help that
person. And while that's a great noble
idea, that's not what actually is going
to produce profitability for you. So
when you're marketing, you want to
figure out what are the deepest desires
as well as what are the biggest
frustrations
that are preventing them from getting to
those desires? What have they tried
before already? There's a great book
that's out there that I recommend to all
my clients called The Ultimate Sales
Letter. It's by Dan Kennedy. It's right
here,
The Ultimate Sales Letter by Dan
Kennedy. And he talks about in this
book, the 10 smart market diagnosis
questions.
What keeps them up at night? What are
they afraid of? What are they angry
about? What are their top daily
frustrations? What trends are occurring?
What do they secretly and ardently
desire the most? These are deep, even
repressed desires that they won't tell
anybody about. And that's when you
figure out the niche. What built-in bias
do they have? Do they have their own
language? Who else is selling to them
something similar?
And who else has tried something selling
something to them and has failed in the
past? And so when you can put all of
that together, you can start to market
to this group of people. You can start
to find them on the internet. They
exist. They're out there. They're people
that are looking for exactly what you
offer. you can find those people and
give them their desires. And that's what
I do is I look at, okay, the people that
fit my niche, what do they want the
most? What do they really want to learn
right now? What's a quick win that they
want to learn? So then what I figure out
is I figure out, okay, I have my
coaching program right here. This has
we have over almost 40 courses in the
coaching program inside my wealthy coach
academy program. You can get a 14-day
trial of my program just to see is it
for me? Is it going to produce the
results that I want? I'd love to see you
in there and jump in and try it out for
14 days to see that. Okay, we have all
this. What I'll do is I'll I might just
take one of those courses
and then I'm going to create an offer
that's based around that. So, let's say
that I do Instagram ads. I'm going to
teach Instagram ads
as an offer that I can then put out
there to people to attract
based on the desire of a coach that
wants to learn how to use Instagram ads
to be able to get more clients and more
leads in their business. And so I might
take all of the stuff that I do, but I'm
going to pick one thing very
specifically that's connected to a
desire that somebody has.
Well, and that desire is going to be
based off it's based off what are people
asking me the most for. And then from
there, that's the offer that I'm going
to put out there. I can't put all of my
offer out there. I can't put all of my
coaching out there. I'm not, and this is
very important. I'm not going to promote
my whole big coaching program.
That's not what I promote. I promote one
very specific pillar of it to people
because when somebody's a stranger on
the internet and they've not met me
before, even videos like this are a
great example of this. I'm not teaching
my entire coaching model in this video,
but I pick one I cherrypicked one thing.
Finding your niche, figuring out your
niche, and then I will talk about that
one thing. And the idea is is that I use
that to connect people to my wealthy
coach academy program. I use that to
connect people to my VIP program where I
actually build your business with you.
And from there, I'm able to then find
people that the algorithm sends to me,
that the advertising platform send to
me,
and I'm able to tell those people about
my programs that I have to offer. I get
to make incredible offers like this
14-day trial that we offer completely
free, risk-f free to be able to jump
into the Wealthy Coach Academy program
by baiting the hook with what is the
desire that somebody has. So, if
somebody's like, I want to figure out my
niche. We help you with that and we show
you exactly how to monetize it, exactly
what to do and what to say to get the
kind of clients that you want. if you've
tried things before. Our program is
different because it gets results
consistently for our clients.
And so that's what we do is we figure
out what is one key area that's based on
a pillar of what we help people with.
And then that's what we put out there.
We put that out there in the form of
content. We put that out there in the
form of lead magnets that get people's
name and email address on our email
list. But we use all of those to then
direct people over to
what do we have for sale?
What is the offer that we have? What is
the coaching program that we have? What
is that thing that we have that we're
offering that's going to monetize and
get people results? And what you want to
do is you want to sell the result and
the transformation over here.
You want to create an offer that
generates leads and interest based on
one of the pillars along the way and the
first step of what it takes to get to
the result and transformation that you
offer.
I can't give you a life transformation
here in one video or even one webinar or
one training. But if you come alongside
me and work with me and I get to walk
with you every day in your business, we
can get you results. And so that's what
the Wealthy Coach Academy program is
for. That's why it's so valuable. That's
why it's so incredible.
But when we have a video like this about
finding your niche or we have a video
about running Facebook ads, those are a
very specific offer based on the desire
that somebody has to be able to get that
specific result. Okay? So like this
whole example that I just gave you of
how I do that, that's exactly what you
do in your business. You figure out what
is the niche? How do I help somebody?
What is their ardent desire that they
have? And then you want to start to
build offers around those specific
desires. What is one very specific quick
win that you can get people that then
leads directly to the thing that you
offer for sale? And if you don't have a
coaching program created, you want to
start with that. You want to start by
creating a program around those things.
We have a number of great chat GPT
prompts that you can check out as well
in our chat GBT prompt document. If you
just go over to my website over at
jeremiacowski.com,
it's at the top of the website right
here. You're going to have to go find it
yourself, but free AI prompts right
here. And one of the top prompts that's
in there is it's this prompt that
generates an entire business plan for
you. Master marketing ideas prompt. It
comes with the whole coaching program in
your specified niche. Detailed
instructions on all the components,
multiple marketing materials, and then
below that, we have a number of great
prompts for sales copy as well that you
can check out. this document. We put it
together. It's over 44 pages long. Has
some of the best AI prompts that you'll
find anywhere. Absolutely free right
over there on my website. Okay. So, if
you're a coach, if you're a mentor, this
is going to make you more money by
figuring out what do they desire the
most, creating an offer around it, and
that actually becomes the niche for your
offer that you're promoting. That's
actually what's going to get the most
results for you. It goes beyond just,
oh, I help doctors or I help, you know,
brain surgeons or I help hair
estheticians,
but what very specifically are they
struggling with? And then do they
desire? You want to go based around
those desires.
Give people that quick win of that
desire and use it to lead people to what
you have for sale. And that's the best
way to find the most profitable and most
marketable niches in your business for
what your offers will be. Listen, if
this has helped you, share it with
somebody and jump into my Wealthy Coach
Academy program. Try it out for 14 days.
We'll see you in there.
[Applause]
[Music]